ice-watch.com 2017-06-30

# Ice-Watch

[ __ ](https://www.ice-watch.com/be-en/ "Return to Home") > [About](https://www.ice-watch.com/be-en/contenu/about.cfm "About") > Privacy Policy

September 2015

**Visiting ICE's _[ice-watch.com](https://www.ice-watch.com/be-en/)_ website (the “Website”) confirms that you agree and understand the terms of our privacy policy ("Privacy Policy")**. **If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, or any modification(s) thereto, please exit the Website now and do not purchase any of the products offered for sale on the Website.**

This Website and in particular the sale of watches is operated by Supplies Distributors SA, rue Louis Blériot 5, 4460 Grâce-Hollogne, Belgium (company number: 0475.286.142; VAT BE 0475.286.142) (hereafter "SDSA") in its own name, as a business partner of ICE SA S.A.(“ICE”). ICE has created this Privacy Policy in order to communicate ICE's policies and practices relating to the collection, use and disclosure of personal information i.e. information that identifies an individual, which we collect when you use the Website, namely, your name, gender, postal address (including billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, fax number, email address, credit and debit card information ("PI").

This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with PI that we collect through this Website. We may change this Privacy Policy by posting a new privacy policy on the Website. You can determine when this Privacy Policy was last revised by referring to the legend at the top of this page. Any changes to our Privacy Policy will become effective upon our posting of the revised Privacy Policy on the Website. However, all significant changes to our Privacy Policy, which would lower the protection of your PI already provided to us, will only become effective upon receiving your explicit consent.

**What information is collected on the Website?**

You may use the Website without providing any PI to ICE. You will however need to provide PI if you choose to (i) purchase products offered on the Website for the purposes of paying for the products you ordered and processing your order (ii) contact us. Any information you provide on the Website may be processed in Europe and United States of America.

You allow ICE and SDSA to store this PI in the ICE customer database. Your PI are kept five years.

You may request by sending an e-mail to ICE to modify or delete your PI at any time as soon as your order has been processed and delivered (see "Changes and access to your PI”). ICE and SDSA may collect non-personal information about you even if you do not purchase any products on the Website.

**Newsletters**

ICE also provides you, upon your prior approval, with the opportunity to receive information from ICE, which may be of interest to you, including information relating to products offered on the Website. If you do not want any more to receive such information by e-mail, you may opt-out of further communications at any time by contacting ICE at _[info@ice-watch.com](mailto:info@ice-watch.com)_ or by calling us at +32 61 21 71 00.

**What use is made of the information you provide?**

We may use and process your PI for the following purposes:

  * fulfil your requests, such as to respond to a question regarding our products, to help you locate a store near you, fulfil your order, process your payment card, and/or to provide you with customer service;
  * send you important information regarding the Website, changes to our terms, conditions, and policies and/or other administrative information;
  * inform you of products, programs, services and promotions that we believe may be of interest to you (upon having received your according consent to do so);
  * allow you to send email to others through our "send to a friend" application or publish content on social media type functionality;
  * allow you to participate in contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities. Some of these activities have additional rules, which could contain additional information about how we use and disclose your PI;
  * customize content for you on our Website and provide you with customized offers;
  * facilitate our internal business purposes , namely data analysis, audits, developing new products, enhancing our Website, improving our services, identifying usage trends and determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;
  * prevent or detect any misuse or fraud;
  * identify you to any person to whom you send messages through the Website;

and only to the extent it is permitted (a) under applicable laws; (b) to comply with legal process (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; and (g) to permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.

Please note that

  * when you freely post information and materials including a survey for research purposes any information you post or disclose through these services (for example, PI contained in the photos, stories, comments and videos that you submit) may become public information, and may be available to visitors to the Website and to the general public;
  * in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets or stock (including without limitation in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings), the Privacy Policy will stay applicable and in force.

ICE and SDSA may disclose the PI you provide on the Website to (i) delivery company, in order to process your order and deliver it to you; (ii) third parties who provide services on or to the Website including web hosting, data analysis, IT services, e-mail delivery services, survey fulfilment, social media applications; (iii) any party which has to verify your information, authenticate payments and process orders.

ICE may also disclose, with your prior approval, the  PI you provide on the Website to other companies in the ICE group, in order that such corporate affiliates may contact you with respect to information about such corporate affiliates, including products and services of such corporate affiliates that may be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive such information by email, you may opt out as set forth above in the section entitled "Newsletter".

**Other information**

ICE, SDSA  and our third party service providers may collect other Information from you, namely your IP address, MAC address, your computer type, screen resolution, OS version and Internet browser, as well as information collected through the use of cookies, pixel tags, web beacons, and other similar technologies to better serve you with more tailored information and facilitate your ongoing use of the Website. ICE, SDSA our third party service providers may also collect other Information, namely demographic data, for example your city or state as well as aggregate PI in a manner such that the end-product does not personally identify you or any other user of the Website, for example, by using PI to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code.

**Sensitive information**

Please do not send us, or disclose, any sensitive personal information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, criminal background or trade union membership) on or through the Website.

**Links**

The Website contains links to other third party websites. This Privacy Policy does not address and ICE/SDSA are note responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information by any third parties, on other websites or offline. In some cases, we may permit you to use third-party payment services to make payments. If you wish to make a payment using a payment service, you will be directed to a webpage that is hosted by the payment service and not by us. Any information that you provide through a payment service will be subject to its privacy policy, and not this Privacy Policy. You should carefully review the privacy policies of any third party websites and contact the operators of those websites if you have any questions about their use of your information.

**Security**

ICE has implemented security measures to protect the PI you provide against unauthorized access and use. All financial information you provide on the Website is stored on a secure Website operated by SDSA's financial institution. Transactions conducted on Website are protected by an SSL encrypting system. Please be aware, however, that no data transmission over the Internet is 100% secure and any information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used by persons other than the intended recipient.

**Payment**

If you pay with a payment card that is issued by a bank located in a country outside the European Union, then your payment data can be sent to that country as well, in order to enable the processing of your payment. By submitting your payment card details you expressly agree that your payment data can be sent to this non EU-country. 

**Changes and access to your PI – your rights**

You may ask ICE for access to or to correct, update or delete information you have provided to ICE by contacting ICE, among others to ensure that your orders are shipped to the correct address and that we can contact you about your order if necessary. You may opt-out of further communications at any time. ICE may also retain, for archival purposes, copies of communications with users of the Website and any response to questions or comments sent to users by ICE/SDSA.

**Contact us**

ICE SA S.A., Place McAuliffe 34, 6600 Bastogne, Belgium ( _[privacy@ice-watch.com](mailto:info@ice-watch.com)_ ); phone number +32 61 21 71 00 is your data controller according to the Directive on the Protection of Personal Data 95/46/EC and SDSA and its parent company PFSWEB, Inc. shall be Data Processors. The PI will primarily be processed by SDSA, however, please be aware that PI may also be transferred and processed by any entity within the ICE Group located in the European Union with the objective to process the PI in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In the event that PI are transferred and processed by an entity within the ICE Group, this entity will also be considered the Data Processor, therefore when ICE is mentioned in this document in the role of the Data Controller, this may also be construed to apply to the relevant ICE entity.

PFSWEB, Inc. (parent company of SDSA) is incorporated in the United States of America and is participant in the Safe Harbour program developed by the US Department of Commerce and the European Union. PFSWEB, Inc. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbour Privacy Principles agreed upon by the US and the EU. For more information about the Safe Harbour and to view the certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbour website: _<https://safeharbor.export.gov/companyinfo.aspx?id=26292>_.
